Cook, Alice Papers /3012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Series VII: Publications and Writings
  - Sub-Series C. Bibliographic - Card Files (in metal boxes)
    - Foreign-Canada - Foreign-Russia; US Pre 1980- 1-2 (Box 111)
    - US Pre 1980- 3; Women (Box 112)
    - United Teachers (Box 113-115)
    - Union Democracy; Public Employee Press; Socialism; Union and Community; New Deal (Box 116)
    - Teachers; Foreign; Japan (Box 117)
    - Professions; Classic Readings; NY Times (index of articles) (Box 118)
    - General Labor (Box 119)
- Series VIII: Diaries, Travel Logs, Journals, Notes (Box 120)
  - Australia (Box 120, Folder 1-3)
  - China (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Germany (Box 120, Folder 5-9)
  - Great Britain (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Hawaii (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Hong Kong (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Japan (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous countries (Box 120, Folder 14-16)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 120, Folder 17-22)
  - Sweden (Box 120, Folder 23-24)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Uppsala, Vienna) (Box 120, Folder 25-26)
  - Series IX: Miscellaneous (Box 121)
  - Retirement, 1972 (Box 121, Folder 1-3)
    Correspondence from friends, colleagues, and former students commemorating her retirement
  - Eightieth Birthday, 1983 (Box 121, Folder 4-7)
    Correspondence from friends, colleagues, and former students commemorating her eightieth birthday
  - Ninetieth Birthday, 1993 (Box 121, Folder 8-11)
  - Photograph (Box 122, Folder 1)
    undated
  - Photographs: Retirement Celebration, 1972 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Ninetieth birthday, 1993 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Photographs (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Interviews Biographical Reminiscences, 1981 (Box 122, Folder 5-7)
  - Interviews Cornell Program in Oral History, 1981 (Box 122, Folder 8-9)
  - Articles re: Cook (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Articles re: Northwestern Degree, 1988 (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Address book of A. Hanson and W. Cook (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Notebook labelled "Kendall" (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Handwritten notes re: workplace programs (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Pamphlets: travel brochures from India and Israel (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Handwritten notes re: trade unions (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook containing newspaper articles, 1937 (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Articles in French, 1971-1975 (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 122, Folder 19-21)
  - Senate Case, 1971 (Box 122, Folder 22-28)
    Materials pertaining to suit of Kaye, Scholer, Fierman, Hays, and Handler v. Erk et al, in which Alice Cook was named as a defendant. The case concerned the collection of legal fees, collective bargaining and the Faculty Senate of the State University of New York
- Series Series X: Memorabilia
  - Memorabilia (Box 122, Folder 29-30)
    Awards received by Alice Cook from Northwestern University Alumni Association and Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA)
  - Regalia and Plaques (Box 123)
  - Card file: ILR 366 "Women at Work" Lecture Notes (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Card File: Women at Work, 1977 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Desk name plate for Alice B. Cook (Box 125, Folder 3)
    Nameplate: "Alice H. Cook" (mother-of-pearl inlay)